REPORTER : Tomorrow marks the one year anniversary
since Velez Sir Flight 180 exploded and crashed
shortly after takeoff from JFK airport .
It 's a disaster that 's affected many .
None more so than Mt . Abraham High School ,
which lost 40 students and four faculty members in the crash .
But it was the events after the crash
that has turned this tragic story
into something even stranger .
The survivors who managed to get off the plane before it crashed
died soon thereafter in a series
of mysterious and bizarre accidents .
Now , to some , these deaths are just tragic coincidences ,
but to others , they 're an indication
that there are more sinister events taking place .
That 's the contention of tonight 's guest .
Thank you for joining us this evening .
MAN : Thank you for having me .
And I appreciate you using the word sinister .
Most people say supernatural because they think I 'm talking
about ghosts and witches and stuff like that .
REPORTER : Here 's your chance to set the record straight .
MAN : Great . Okay .
I believe that there 's a sort of force ,
an unseen malevolent presence ...
That 's all around us every day .
And it determines when we live and die .
And some people call this force the devil ,
but I think that whole religious thing is- -
so I prefer to call it death itself .
REPORTER : So I 'm surrounded by death ?
MAN : Absolutely . Absolutely .
Every day , everywhere , all the time .
And that 's what I want people to understand- -
that death has this grand design
that we all fit into .
So when Alex Browning got off that plane
and took the other survivors with him ,
he basically screwed up death 's plan .
And that 's what I 'm trying to warn people about .
REPORTER : And the fact that all of the survivors have died
is your evidence of this ?
MAN : Well , it 's not so much that the survivors died ,
but it 's the way that they died .
I mean , there were so many weird ,
seemingly random things about the way they died .
It just didn 't make sense .
And that 's the proof there 's something out there- -
REPORTER : Wait , that 's not proof . That is your interpretation
of events that can 't be proven in order to support your ideas .
- [ WIND HOWLING ] - DEEP VOICE : Kimberly .
MAN : You should be more open-minded about- -
REPORTER : What happened after that was just coincidence .
MAN : May I finish ?
Mere coincidence would have one or two of these kids die .
But not all of them including their teachers .
REPORTER : Yes , but people die all the time ,
so why should this be any different ?
It forced people to question
these so-called everyday coincidences .
What if they were something more ?
What if you could do something about it ?
Please , are you listening to yourself ? This is crazy .
You 're saying we should be on guard every morning when we leave the house ?
MAN : That 's exactly what I 'm saying .
- [ DOOR SLAMS ] - Exactly it .
And in order to survive- -
the only way to survive
is to look beneath the visible world .
Because in the end no one can escape death .
And today may be your day to die .
Okay , I 'll call you .
Kimberly , are you sure you 've got everything ?
Credit card , cell phone , triple-a card ?
Dad , it 's Daytona , not Somalia .
All right . Fix-a-flat , road flares , sunblock , mace ?
Condoms , whips , chains .
Just kidding , Mr. Corman .
Don 't worry , I 'll keep an eye on her .
That makes me feel a lot better , thanks .
- Okay . - All righty .
WOMAN : Can we go get the guys ? I 'm getting horny .
[ GIGGLING ]
Go on .
Okay , I 'll call you .
Whips and chains . That 's nice .
Whatever , your dad 's cool .
- [ LAUGHS ] - [ ROCK MUSIC PLAYS ]
Buckle up !
- WOMAN : Watch it ! - [ TIRES SCREECH ]
- Oh , easy , Kimmy . First year of driving ? - Sorry .
[ LAUGHTER ]
- Oh my God . - MAN : Fucking freak .
Yo , Dano , shouldn 't we help your mom ?
Good one , man . You 're hilarious .
You 're not getting any of my weed . Nothing .
Whatever .
MAN : What are we going to do in Daytona ?
DANO : We 're going to see lots of honeys there .
We 're gonna get drunk , we 're gonna smoke this big " El gagerero , "
we 're gonna have this awesome party ...
[ CHANTING ] Pileup ! Pileup !
ANNOUNCER : A candlelight vigil to mark the one year anniversary
of the crash of flight 180 will be held at 8 : 00 P.M. tonight
at the Mt . Abraham High School auditorium .
♪ Highway to hell ...
[ SOFT ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
[ MEN LAUGHING ]
Oh my God .
[ RINGING ]
- Hello ? - Hey , Kimberly , it 's dad .
Hey , what 's up ?
Listen , your car 's leaking transmission fluid .
So I want you to get it checked right away .
Okay , yeah .
KIMBERLY : I 'll do that .
MR. CORMAN : I mean it . Take care of it .
[ COUGHING ]
- Is that someone coughing ? - Yeah , okay .
I 'll take care of it . I 'll talk to you later .
- I love you . - Bye , honey .
- What did you do ? - Look at those titties !
- Shut up . - You missed that ? !
That 's too bad . That 's too bad .
DANO : Oh , shit !
Fuck man , there 's a fucking cop behind us !
Pull in the right Lane now !
Shit .
[ HORN BLARING ]
Seriously , put it out .
- Put that thing out . - All right .
Wait , wait , wait !
- Get rid of it . - Shit .
Hey , it 's Kat .
Listen- - what the hell ? !
Just wait . Not you .
[ BEEPING ]
I think we better pull over and check the car , because- -
Kimberly , the car is going to be fine .
Your dad 's going to be fine , you 're going to be fine .
Okay ?
WOMAN : Look at that guy .
He 's drinking a beer .
Oh , yeah , that 's real responsible .
[ LOUD RAP MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO ]
You ever hear of the ozone layer , asshole ? !
[ POP MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ POLICE RADIO CHATTER ]
♪ When it comes to this drug shit I was made to play ♪
♪ don 't come around if you ain 't got no cocaine to bring ... ♪
what ? I 'm wearing my seatbelt .
You 're gonna bust me , bitch ? !
Aaah !
Son of a ...
Bitch .
[ GASPS ]
[ SCREECHING ]
Fuck !
[ SCREAMS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
- Oh my God ! - MAN : Watch out !
- Stop ! - Oh my God !
Watch out ! Aaah !
[ DISTANT SCREAMS ]
- Shaina ? - [ SCREAMING ]
I can 't get out of here !
Help me !
[ SCREAMS ]
Oh , easy , Kimmy . First year of driving ?
[ LAUGHTER ]
Yo , Dano , shouldn 't we help your mom ?
DANO : Good one , man . You 're hilarious .
[ CHANTING ] Pileup ! Pileup !
- Oh my God . - What ?
There 's going to be a huge accident .
We 're all gonna die ! I just saw it .
That 's it . My turn to drive .
- No , I 'm serious . - Kim , what 's wrong ?
[ HONKING ]
- What are you doing ? - Oh my God .
ANNOUNCER : ... Of flight 180 will be held at 8 : 00 P.M. tonight
at the Mt . Abraham High School auditorium .
" Highway to hell . " " Highway to hell ... "
" Highway to hell " ?
♪ I 'm on a highway to hell ... ♪
okay , Kimberly , you 're scaring me .
- DANO : Green means go , Kimmy . - Yeah .
Are you out of your mind ? What the hell are you doing ?
What the fuck , Kimberly ?
What 's this ?
[ HORNS BLARING ]
Kimberly , you just got to breathe .
Oh , shit , shit . Five-o is coming .
- Let 's fucking roll . - What ?
Oh my God .
Do you know how much fucking weed I have on me ?
- Huh ? - Dano , just shut up !
Just stay cool .
[ LOUD RAP MUSIC PLAYING ]
Oh , fuck . I 'm going to jail . I 'm fucking going to jail .
What 's going on here ?
I think there 's going to be a huge pileup .
I saw it .
There were bodies everywhere .
There were logs- - I saw it .
It just happened .
All right , miss , I 'd like you to please step out of the vehicle .
[ HORN BLARES ]
Just pull over !
I know , mommy 's hungry , too .
Come on .
[ SIGHS ] Come on !
Oh , fuck this .
I 'm going to get this and we 're going to go .
[ ENGINE SHUTS OFF ]
Fuck .
What the hell is going on up there ?
WOMAN : Excuse me !
Is there any way that we could drive around ?
- I have a delivery- -
- You need to get back into your vehicles .
- Just move it- - - now !
That 's it !
That 's the truck that 's going to kill everybody .
You need to stop that truck !
I told you again , you have to calm down !
- Why won 't you listen to me ? ! - [ HORNS HONKING , CRASHING ]
- Fuck ! - Oh my God .
This is unit 13 requesting medical assistance
and backup for a major traffic accident ...
Kimberly , what 's going on ?
No !
Listen , sir , this girl is really freaked out .
In fact , all of them are scared as you can imagine .
Scared ? !
These people are the luckiest sons of bitches on the planet .
Get this guy , Evan Lewis- -
yesterday the kid wins the lotto .
Today , some loony bitch blocks traffic
and he avoids the worst pileup in years .
I should be so damn " unlucky . "
Go babysit the rest of them .
I 'll be done with Lewis in a minute .
- Hey , excuse me- - - [ ALL SHOUTING ]
We 're trying to do the best we can .
We 're going to get you out of here as soon as possible .
MAN : I just think it 's a bunch of bullshit .
Listen , I know you 've gone over all this
with detective Suby ...
But would you mind telling me what happened ?
It was like I was there .
I knew something bad was going to happen even before it did .
I just felt wrong , just like ...
Just like what ?
Look , I know this sounds crazy but ...
You guys all heard about flight 180 , right ?
The kid who got off the plane ?
Well , it happened a year ago , today .
My premonition was just like his .
- What are you talking about ? - MAN : Come on .
You must have read about the kid
who had a dream about a plane blowing up ,
so he got all his buddies off the plane
and then the thing blew up just like in his dream ?
- Yeah . - But did you hear what happened after ?
So a month goes by , right ?
Everything seems cool .
But then all the survivors start to die one-by-one .
'Cause when your number 's up , your number 's up , right ?
You know , some people even say that death itself was stalking them ,
hunting each one down
until they were all ... Dead .
[ SINISTER LAUGH ]
Please .
OFFICER : There was one survivor .
Clear Rivers is in a padded room
at the Stonybrook Institution .
Well , that 's encouraging .
KAT : Okay , you want me to believe this is true ,
that this is happening all over again ?
I don 't know why we 're even here .
What do you want from me ?
But if I was never meant to pull over ,
we all should have died in that pileup .
Which means death could be coming for us .
MAN : Yeah , like ...
What if we 're all getting that " different strokes " curse or something ?
I think you 're all are certifiable .
I can 't believe I 've been listening to this crap .
Let 's go . Let 's go , Tim .
Mrs. Carpenter , please .
MR. CORMAN : Kimberly !
Oh baby !
- Are you okay ? - I 'm so sorry .
Shh , shh .
You can all go now . Thank you for your patience .
Could I ask you something ?
Anything .
Did mom ever have any ...
I don 't know , weird feelings about anything ?
What do you mean ?
Like visions or premonitions .
Sweetie , are you sure you 're okay ?
Dad , I know this sounds crazy ,
but I 'm really scared for the others .
I don 't know , I have this really bad feeling .
What ?
It 's not over yet .
[ DOOR SQUEAKS ]
Jesus Christ !
Shit !
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ MACHINE BEEPS , REWINDS ]
WOMAN : Hey , Evan , it 's Tawny .
Sorry I haven 't called .
Hey , listen , I heard about your lottery win .
Let 's hook up . Call me .
- [ MACHINE BEEPS ] - Yeah .
Hi , Evan , it 's Nikki .
We met at Tucker 's party last year ?
I know it 's been awhile , but I 've been thinking about you .
- [ LOUD BANG ] - I just wanted to say congratulations .
- So give me a call . - [ LOUD BANG ]
555-0123 . Bye .
You little bastard .
Shit .
Come on . Come on .
Fuck . Fuck .
Come on !
Come on .
[ ALARM BEEPING ]
Fuck !
Jesus !
Oh !
[ PHONE RINGING ]
Hey , this is Evan . Leave a message .
If you 're looking for Rick , I don 't know where he is ,
and I don 't know when he 's coming back . Thanks .
MAN : Evan , call me when you get in , you lucky fuck !
[ BEEP FADES , STOPS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
Come on ! Come on ! Come on !
Aah !
[ YELLS ]
Jesus !
Come on .
Aah !
Shit , I 'm lucky .
Jesus Christ !
No , mother ,
just turn on any station .
Well , I don 't know how you missed it , it 's been on all day .
Yes , mother , channel 4 is fine .
Okay- - here it is ! I got to go , okay ?
I got to go !
To recap our top story ,
route 23 was backed up for almost nine hours today .
MAN : A record-breaking pileup killed an estimated 18 people .
Emergency crews spent hours sifting through the wreckage
hoping to recover any survivors from this tragic collision .
So far police are refusing to release the names of the victims
until the families are notified .
The camera of a highway patrol car
managed to catch this shocking footage .
- A semi comes ... - Oh my God .
And smashes into a red SUV .
- The driver of the SUV ... - No , um ...
Leave it .
... may have saved her life .
He pulled her back at the last second
just as the semi plowed into the vehicle .
The passengers inside the SUV ...
Oh , oh , oh ! You guys see that ? ! Shit , I was there , baby !
In other news , a freak accident took the life of a lotto winner .
- Friends say Evan Lewis ... - Hey , shh .
Was on top of the world after recently winning $ 250,000 .
But in tragic turn of events , Lewis died today
while trying to escape a fire in his apartment .
He managed to make it out of the building ,
but somehow the ladder on the fire escape
slipped and impaled him .
Investigators believe Lewis died instantly .
- [ KNOCKING ] - Come in .
Hey , buddy .
I want you to take this so you can get some sleep .
And then tomorrow it 's off to the dentist , which I know you love .
Now , get some rest .
- Mom . - Yeah ?
You think those guys were bsing us today ?
Yeah .
Some people just need some rewiring , that 's all .
Lights out .
[ THUNDER RUMBLES ]
DOCTOR : At the request of the patient ,
you 'll relinquish any sharp objects
such as : Nail files , pencils , pens ,
safety pins , bobby pins , your necklace ,
matches , lighters , belts , belt buckles ,
earrings , hair clips , glasses , shoelaces ,
paper clips , watches , money clip , pocket knives ,
food , drinks , keys , cell phone- -
you have a cell phone on you ?
- -poisons , pills , medications .
Great . And let me see your nails .
Good . Then I think we 're all done .
Wait .
Is she dangerous or something ?
No , honey , she expects you are .
MAN : Get him off me . Get him off me !
How long are they gonna keep her locked up like this ?
Depends on her , I guess . She 's voluntary .
- Clear Rivers ? - Don 't come any closer .
They told me you had something to do
with the crash on route 23 .
Look , I don 't know how to explain it ,
but I saw the pileup before it happened .
And I saved some people .
And now you think death is after you .
Nice work .
Maybe if you 're real lucky , you 'll wind up in here with me .
Anything else ?
One of the people died in a freak accident last night .
What if the other people are in danger , too ?
If you put them on the list , they 're already dead .
List ? What list ?
Death 's list .
The survivors of flight 180
died in the exact order
they were originally meant to die in the plane crash .
That was death 's original design .
The list .
I was supposed to die in that crash with my friends .
So you 're telling me that I 'm next ?
You said someone else died last night .
That means someone must have intervened .
Officer Burke pulled me away from the crash that killed my friends .
Congratulations .
You 'll be the last to go .
But don 't worry , once the others are dead ,
it 'll come back for you .
It always does .
This doesn 't make sense .
You said that you die in the order you 're originally meant to .
But my friends died last in my premonition , not first .
Wait .
Dead last ?
Backwards .
Are you sure ?
KIMBERLY : In my premonition
that Nora woman and her kid died .
Then Evan , then me and my friends .
Why is this even happening to me ?
That 's what Alex used to ask himself .
So , what am I supposed to do ?
Clear .
Watch out for the signs .
What ?
Have you ever seen anything creepy or ominous ?
An in-your-face irony kind of thing ?
The songs on the radio .
Yeah , the guy in the beer truck , everything on the road .
CLEAR : Well , don 't ignore it .
Recognizing those signs usually means
the difference between life and death .
You got to help me .
I don 't have to do anything .
But you beat it .
Take a look around .
What did I beat , Kimberly ?
If you were smart , you 'd save yourself
and just forget about the others .
How can you say that ? You have a responsibility .
My friends are dead .
That 's how I can say that .
This is what happened to Alex when I was responsible for him .
Get out .
Before you hurt me or yourself .
- All right , you know what ? - What ?
I think you 're a coward .
You hide out in here because you 're
too damn bitter and selfish to help any other person .
In my opinion , you 're already dead .
BURKE : I tried calling you last night ,
but your father said you were sleeping .
- Evan Lewis is dead . - Yeah .
I 've been getting calls all morning from everyone who was on the on-ramp .
We 're meeting tonight at my apartment .
Wait , so ... You believe all this death stuff ?
Well , at first , no , I didn 't .
Until last year when I was dispatched
to clean up one of the flight 180 survivors .
Clean up , I don 't- -
- did you see that ? - See what ?
- Pigeons . - Pigeons ?
- It 's a sign . - A sign of what ?
If Clear 's right about the order ,
then Nora and Tim are going to be attacked by pigeons .
I 'm not following you .
They 're next on death 's list .
If we don 't find them , they 're going to die .
[ NURSE CLEARS THROAT ]
The doctor 's ready for you , now .
If he gives me the gas
and I wake up with my pants unbuttoned ...
- We ain 't paying . - [ LAUGHS ] Tim .
[ DISTANT JACKHAMMERING ]
There you are .
What happened to you yesterday , Tim ?
We missed you in here .
We got hung up by that accident on route 23 .
Good lord . How lucky that you 're okay .
Your mom says you 've been having some pain lately .
Not really .
[ JACKHAMMERING CONTINUING ]
I 'm a bit disappointed , Tim .
Does your mom know you 've been smoking ?
Uh-huh .
Ow .
Yeah , that one 's going to have to be filled .
[ THUDS ]
Damn those pigeons .
How many times am I going to have to replace those goddamn windows ?
[ WORKER SHOUTING ] We can 't do it , boss , we can 't do it !
This will only sting for a moment .
Open big .
Little bit wider .
Wider .
Okay .
- [ RUMBLING ] - Oh God .
How do they expect me to ...
Would you rather just have the laughing gas ?
- Yeah . - Okay .
Jean , I 'm going to need you in here .
You 're have to speak up , there 's too much noise .
- [ JACKHAMMERING CONTINUING ] - What ? ! I can 't hear you !
Excuse me , what ? !
Yes , the sixth at 2 : 00 P.M.
Jean ! Let me get this started .
[ GAS HISSING ]
Tim , you 'll be awake and a little groggy ,
but you 're not going to be able to move much .
[ DRILL WHIRRING ]
Okay , great , thanks . All right , turn around .
The cleaning lady said they 're at the Ellis Medical Complex off of 14th .
- [ GLASS SHATTERS ] - Goddamn it anyway .
- Okay , I got it . - I can 't find a box !
[ SHOUTING ]
DOCTOR : Not again . Careful .
[ GROANING ]
There we go .
DOCTOR : Jean , how is Tim doing in there ?
What did he say about your tooth ?
- Did he say- - - I can 't remember .
- Nora ! - The pigeons !
What ? Pigeons ?
MAN : Hey , whoa , whoa ! Kid , kid !
- No-oo ! - Tim !
MAN : Look out !
- Stay back , stay back ! - No ! Please , no !
[ NORA SOBBING ]
Nora 's not coming . She won 't leave her son .
- No , but she 's next- - - Right now I don 't think she cares .
This is really happening again , isn 't it ?
I hoped we 'd get there
and they 'd be fine ,
and Clear Rivers was just full of shit ,
and Evan Lewis ' death was just some freak accident .
But we 're all going to die , aren 't we ?
I 'm so scared .
I know you didn 't ask for any of this ...
But I don 't think you have it in you to quit either .
A second one just died .
A 15-year-old kid .
I hope you 're ready for this .
It 's this way .
BURKE : How is this guy going to help us anyway ?
CLEAR : He seemed to know a hell of a lot more
about death than he ever told us .
Shouldn 't we knock first ?
He probably already knows we 're coming .
Hello , Clear .
I 've been expecting you .
Oh my God .
- That 's Evan Lewis . - Come to pick my brain ?
Just a simple question and we 'll leave you alone with your new friend .
Dead ...
Yet still fresh .
Look , we drove a long way to get here ,
so if you happen to know how to stop death ,
it would be really great if you told us .
You can 't cheat death .
- There are no escapes . - Bullshit .
You told me death has a distinct design .
But Alex and I cheated death ,
not once but dozens of times .
The design is flawed , it can be beaten .
Such fire in you now .
People are always most alive
just before they die .
Don 't you think ?
[ WHISTLING ]
Look , please ...
If you know of anything that could help us ,
what harm could it do ?
Only new life can defeat death .
What the hell does that mean ?
Some people say there 's a balance to everything .
For every life there 's a death ,
and for every death there is a life .
But the introduction of life that was not meant to be ,
that can invalidate the list ,
force death to start anew .
You have to follow the signs ...
Kimberly .
How do you know my name ?
- SKATER : Whoa ! - BURKE : Wait a second .
" New life defeats death " ? " Follow the signs " ?
Where did you find that guy ?
I thought he was supposed to help us ,
not freak us out .
What the fuck are you thinking ? !
[ SCOFFS ]
I 'm thinking suck on my junk , bee-atch .
Little punk .
- [ COUGHING ] - What is it ?
- What did you see ? - [ CAR HORN BLARING ]
You have to tell us , what did you see ?
Kimberly , look at me ! You have to tell us .
- What did you see ? ! - [ GASPING ]
I was driving a white van .
I don 't know , I must have lost control ,
because I crashed into a lake .
- And I drowned . - You were there ?
I can practically taste the water in my mouth .
Wait , remember , the on-ramp ?
There was a pregnant woman in a white delivery van .
He said only new life can defeat death .
If she gives birth to a baby
that would 've died in that car crash- -
a brand new soul that was never part of death 's design- -
it throws the whole list out of whack
and we start over with a clean slate .
It seems like a bit of a reach , don 't you think ?
What else could it mean ?
We have to find the pregnant lady 's number .
I don 't have it . She never came to the station .
We have to find her and warn her about the lake so she can stay alive to have the baby .
- That 'll be an easy conversation to have . - How are we gonna find her ?
- There could be thousands of white vans in the state . - Hey !
I 'm a cop , remember ?
Wait , that 's it .
Got it .
With the plate number I can put out an apb .
Here we go .
The vehicle is a delivery van
registered to Marcus and Isabella Hudson .
We should pick them up pretty quickly .
Come on , let 's get to the meeting .
[ ELEVATOR BELL RINGS ]
Hey , hold the door !
Hey , let go of my shoe !
Give me my shoe !
I wrote to management two weeks ago about these friggin ' bumpers .
Is that dogshit , dude ?
Eww .
Oh , you got something on your ...
It 's still there , bro ' . Here , I can get it for you .
No , it 's all right .
I 'll do it if you want me to do it .
[ HEAVY SIGH ]
Just let- - I 'll- - let me do it .
What ?
Hey , man , how you doing ?
Listen , any word on that white van yet ?
Okay , keep checking .
Does anybody have a valium ?
Oh , yeah .
Here .
You 're just going to want to take half of that .
MAN : Keep ' em coming .
If what you 're saying is true ,
that means I 'm next .
This is crazy , people , come on .
First death is stalking us ,
and now premonitions ? What ?
You 're not next , Nora .
Nobody has to be next . That 's the point .
We need to help each other in order to get through this .
This cannot be happening .
See , because my career is at a peak
and I finally met a quality guy .
I just bought a house .
Maybe if you shut the fuck up , you 'll live .
Like I 'm going to take advice from you .
Okay , look , if you know what to look for ,
you have a fighting chance .
If I call and say , I don 't know- - subway- -
get to a high-rise fast .
A place where no subway could ever possibly go .
Get it ?
CLEAR : Okay , you guys , listen- -
just because Kimberly has these visions ,
it doesn 't mean we 're not all capable
of seeing signs to some extent .
EUGENE : Okay , okay , look .
I gotta call bullshit .
I mean , I 've sat here and listened
to all your theories and all your stories ,
and I think it 's just all bullshit .
Call it what you want !
- It 'll keep your ass alive . - Darlin ' , my ass is alive !
Has been all day .
There is nobody after us but you ,
trying to make us all crazy .
I should have seen that coming .
Yeah .
If death is out to get you ,
why don 't you get the hell away from us ?
She 's the only one that 's dealt with this before .
We need to look out for each other from now on .
Sleep in shifts .
We need to safe-proof this deathtrap .
Get you to step out of the van , miss ?
Are you kidding me ?
- What did I do ? - This vehicle 's been reported stolen .
Ohh !
Screw this . I 'm going for a smoke .
No , no , no , it 's not safe out there .
So , Nora 's got to bite it before me anyhow , huh ?
[ GIGGLES ]
Oh , you people have no sense of humor .
Nora , you okay ?
Four years ago my husband died .
Now Tim . There 's nothing left for me .
Don 't say that , okay ?
If it is my time to go and be in heaven ...
With my family , I can accept that .
You got to trust me . We can fight this .
If we just stick together long enough
for her to have her baby- -
if you 'll excuse me , I have a funeral to plan .
Nora .
What do you think you 're doing ?
- I 'm finished . I 'm out . - Don 't leave , Eugene .
Look , look .
I control my life , all right ?
Not some crazy list death has put together .
I 'll be sure to carve that into your tombstone .
EUGENE : Whatever . You may be able to scare these people ,
- but I 'm not buying that shit . - MAN : Be careful , man .
- Hey . - What ?
Even if you don 't believe , give this to Nora .
I 'm just going to put this in the ...
Closet .
[ SCREAMING ]
Sorry .
Whoa .
Man with hooks ?
Man with hooks .
Hey , I think I see a man with hooks .
Is that ...
- A sign ? - CLEAR : Oh my God .
- Do you guys see that ? - He 's right .
- The phone . - Shit .
[ SNIFFING ]
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
[ SILENT ]
[ CELL PHONE RINGING ]
- Hello ? - Nora !
- Who is this ? - Can you hear me ? !
Officer Burke , I can 't- -
I can 't hear you ! What ? !
What does he- - what ? !
A man with hooks is going to kill you .
- What , what ? - Oh ...
What is it , Nora ?
No !
- Wait , wait ! - Let go !
Wait , wait , Nora !
- Get me out of here ! - Will you stop it ? !
Let me help !
Let me go !
[ SCREAMING ]
Let go of me !
Kat !
Help me !
- Wait ! - I don 't want to die !
[ YELLING ]
Aah !
I got it , thanks . They found the van .
Isabella 's being held at the Greenwood Lake Sheriff 's station .
EUGENE : I 'm in control of my life !
- Kiss my ass ! - Eugene , what is it ?
- I control my life ! - What happened , Eugene ?
- You hear me , you reaper cocksucker ? ! - Calm down .
- What happened ? Where 's Nora ? - Back the fuck up !
- Whoa , whoa , okay ! - Back the fuck up !
Eugene , what 's wrong ? Just tell us what happened .
BURKE : All right , give me the gun , Eugene .
- Give me the gun . - No ! Fuck no !
Eugene , you just got to relax , bro ' , okay ?
You just got to calm down , man .
Give me the gun . Give me the gun , Eugene !
- No , no , no , no ! - Don 't do it ! Don 't do it !
- I ain 't going out like that . - Hey , Eugene , no !
- On my terms ! - Oh my God !
- You hear me ! - [ GUN CLICKS ]
- God ! - [ CLICKING CONTINUES ]
Oh !
You don 't keep it loaded ?
- Maybe they 're all duds . - Six in a row ?
Never . That 's impossible .
It wasn 't his turn to die .
Can we find the pregnant woman , now , please ?
Is this safe , guys ?
I mean , someone in this car is about to get whacked .
Do the rest of us really feel like sitting next to him ?
Or her ?
[ WHISPERS ] Hopefully her .
Okay , guys , let 's not panic .
- Isabella 's safe . - How do you know ?
You said she was going to drive into a lake .
How can she if she 's in protective custody ?
Look at me .
Come on .
Does it look like I 'm in the condition
to commit grand theft auto ? This is insane .
Look , hopefully the district judge
will have it all sorted out by Monday morning , okay ?
Marcus .
Marcus , Marcus .
When I get out of here , I am going to sue his- -
[ WATER SPLASHES ]
- Oh my God . - What , what now ?
My water just broke .
- What ? - My water , it just broke .
- I 'm gonna have my baby . - No , not here .
- No , you can 't do this to me . - Don 't just stand there !
- Get me to a hospital ! - Give me a second to think !
I am not going to have my baby in a jail cell !
Get me to the hospital !
Okay , okay !
Sheriff Perry , this is Deputy Adams , come back .
God , I need the car ! Sheriff Perry , I need the car !
My van ! My van ! Take my van !
Okay . Okay .
Yeah , we 'll go . We 'll go .
Yeah , we 'll go .
Come on , come on !
EUGENE : Y 'all want to hear something crazy ?
It 's not the first time I cheated death .
A kid came to school with a knife- -
killed his teacher .
Teacher would have been me ,
but I was transferred to another school two days before .
That 's fucking weird , man .
You want weird ?
Last year my partner and I were heading out
when a call came in about a train wreck .
Frank decided to let me handle it alone .
He died that night in a shootout .
If that call had come in just 10 seconds later ,
I 'd be dead , too .
Oh my God .
I 'm sorry .
It 's just I got one , too .
Okay , so last may I 'm supposed to go and stay
at this cheesy little bed and breakfast in Pennsylvania .
Anyhow , there 's this major gas leak no one knows about ,
and all the guests suffocated during the night .
- So what happened ? - I don 't know .
I never made it .
The bus I was on splattered some girl over the road .
Was that in Mt . Abraham ?
Yes . How did you know ?
That bus you were on killed Terry chaney .
She was supposed to die on flight 180 .
Hey , do you guys remember that theater in Paris
that collapsed last year and killed everybody inside ?
Well , I had tickets to go .
But one night I 'm in Paris
and I 'm just tripping on acid
and sipping lattes and such .
And then all of a sudden
this dude out of nowhere
just gets whacked by this falling sign .
- Carter . - Wait , wait , wait .
The teacher I replaced , her name was Val Lewton .
She was from Mt . Abraham . She died in an explosion .
Shit . The call about the train wreck
that saved my life ...
That was the night I scraped up Billy Hitchcock .
Wait a minute . Who are these people ?
The people who got off of flight 180 .
CLEAR : They were my friends .
Kimberly , tell us what happened .
About a year ago my mom and I were at the mall .
I was supposed to meet her outside ,
but I got caught up watching this news report
about some kid that committed suicide .
I kept thinking ,
" how can you strangle yourself in the bathtub ?
That 's stupid . "
It felt wrong .
And yet ...
I heard some gunshots and I ran outside .
Some kids were trying to steal my mom 's car .
She tried to fight them off , she was a fighter ,
and they killed her .
After the funeral I kept thinking
that it should have been me .
I guess everyone must think that .
But I guess I was right .
Get there .
Could you drive a little faster maybe ? !
- I 'm going as fast as I can . - God !
CLEAR : When we got off flight 180 ,
it didn 't just change our lives .
It affected everyone and everything
we 've come into contact with since .
I 'm not sure I 'm understanding you .
Being alive after we were supposed to die ,
it caused an outward ripple .
A rift in death 's design .
So if you had never gotten off the plane ...
We wouldn 't be alive in the first place .
Yes , that 's why death is working backwards !
It 's tying up all the loose ends ,
sealing the rift once and for all .
[ SCREAMING ]
Oh , shit !
Jesus Christ !
Hang on ! Hang on !
- Is everybody all right ? - Oh God .
- [ MOANING ] - God , Eugene !
- He can 't breathe . - Oh , my legs !
ISABELLA : No , please .
- It 's not going to wait . - I got to go help those people .
Do you want to deliver this baby ?
Those people can help . Let 's go .
Officer Adams reporting a vehicle collision
off 9-a at the 180 mile-marker .
Send all emergency vehicles to the scene .
- We have to go . Go ! - Okay , okay , okay !
Just- - okay , okay ! We 're going ! We 're going !
- Easy , easy . - Here , here , here .
I think he has a collapsed lung .
- Everyone okay ? - Call an ambulance !
CLEAR : Stay with us .
Hey , hey you !
Hey ! Come on . Help me out .
You got to get me out of here before this thing explodes or something , okay ?
I think it 's okay .
I don 't smell any gas and nothing 's dripping .
All right , get this thing off me . Just pull . Hurry .
Okay . Be careful . Ready ?
Oh God , Jethro ! Jesus Christ !
I got to be able to use my legs when I 'm done .
I 'm so- - dad !
Eugene , everything 's going to be okay .
If he doesn 't get a respirator , he 's not going to make it !
We 're going to get you to the hospital . Be careful with that !
Check the gauges on the regulator ,
and watch out for overdoses !
- And look out for potholes and puddles . - You can 't come in , miss .
And watch out for power lines !
RORY : Watch it !
You trying to get yourself killed , little boy ?
You got to use your head , man .
Thanks .
REPORTER : Okay , let 's go .
How is she doing ?
I think she 's going to be okay .
- Can I ask you a question ? - Yeah .
When I die ...
Is it going to hurt ?
I don 't know .
You 're going to die after me , right ?
Yeah , I guess so .
Would you take these ?
And if I die ...
Will you throw out all my drugs
and my paraphernalia and my porno ?
You know ...
Anything that 's going to break my mom 's heart .
Please ?
Thank you .
WOMAN : This is Cheyenne Jacobson
reporting live from the Gibbons Farm .
Sheriff Perry , officer Burke here .
I 'm trying to get some information on Isabella- -
she did ?
Okay . Thanks . Great . Kimberly !
Isabella 's at Lakeview Hospital . They 're prepping her for delivery .
- We got to go now . - What about Kat ?
I 'll go talk to her .
Hi .
Just find Isabella and get this thing over with , okay ?
Go on , I 'll be fine .
- Where 's Rory ? - I don 't know .
[ MOTOR REVVING ]
Could you be a little quieter with that thing , please ?
Yeah , sure . I 'll just put it on quiet mode .
That would be good .
Rory .
[ TREE CRACKLING ]
FIREFIGHTER : Oh my God !
MAN : Somebody get out there !
- We have to get to the hospital now ! - Well , take my truck !
The keys are in it .
- [ GAGGING ] - CLEAR : Kimberly !
[ MUFFLED SCREAMING ]
- [ BEEPING ] - CLEAR : Kimberly !
- Kimberly . - What do you see ?
- What are we looking for ? - It 's not here .
This one was different .
It was like the van crashing into the lake .
I was in a hospital , there was screaming
and a nurse was trying to choke me .
I couldn 't see her , but I could see her name tag .
It was right in my face . Kalarjian .
I think a nurse named Kalarjian is going to try and kill Isabella .
[ SCREAMING ]
Listen to me , Isabella ! I need you to stop pushing !
What 's wrong ? Is my baby all right ?
The cord 's around the neck . This baby 's in trouble .
REPORTER : A bizarre accident has left two people dead ,
one of them killed by a safety device meant to protect us .
Ironically , the woman was impaled through the head
after her emergency airbag deployed .
She was trapped in her vehicle after it crashed into a field near greenwood lake .
Suddenly the airbag went off ...
[ SIREN BLARING ]
Isabella Hudson ! What room is she in ?
We may need to do a stat caesarean !
Get Dr. Kalarjian up here now !
Dr. Kalarjian , code blue . Delivery room six .
I 'm just going to wait outside ,
'cause I 'm just really in the way here .
- Don 't you dare leave me ! - Okay , okay .
You guys , get to Isabella !
I 'm going to find Eugene !
NURSE : Dr. Kalarjian , code blue . Delivery room six .
Dr. Kalarjian , delivery room six . Code blue .
NURSE : Dr. Kalarjian , in here , hurry !
That 's her .
Wait , wait , wait !
Contractions have stopped .
Arrest in descent halfway through the birth canal .
NURSE : Bad tracing , it 's losing oxygen .
The cord 's compressed !
- Down to 40 . - Oh God ! What 's happening ? !
NURSE : Where 's Kalarjian ? !
BURKE : Dr. Kalarjian !
- Dr. Kalarjian ! - Not now , I 'm busy .
- Ow ! Hey ! Hey ! - Police business .
[ GAGGING ]
ADAMS : Just push a little more .
Oh , no .
Isabella , is the baby okay ?
I 'm sorry . You can 't be here .
- I 'm going to have to ask you to leave . - I need to know- -
- I need to know if the baby 's all right ! - [ BABY CRYING ]
It 's a boy .
Thank you . Congratulations !
Who the hell are they ?
Oh my God !
- Clear . - I can 't find Eugene .
- No , don 't worry . She had the baby ! - It 's okay .
It 's over . It 's okay .
- BURKE : Kimberly . - CLEAR : What did you see ?
I don 't think Isabella was ever supposed to die in that pileup .
Then what 's the premonition of the lake supposed to be ?
Try to remember .
Bloody hands . Someone with bloody hands .
Eugene .
Only new life defeats death . What is that supposed to mean ?
You saw an ecg machine and what else ?
Bloody hands . What else did you see , Kimberly ?
Wait .
Eugene .
[ ALARM RINGING ]
Oh God , no !
Bloody hands .
It 's me . The premonitions are about me .
- What ? - Crash cart .
Let 's go ! Move it !
Dr. Kalarjian .
ECG machine .
The lake .
The white van .
What are you talking about ?
Kimberly : New life .
What is it ?
I know what I have to do to save us .
- I have to die . - No , that 's crazy .
You can 't give up now . We have to fight this thing .
Get Kalarjian .
MORTICIAN : Only new life can defeat death .
NORA : If it is my time to go and be in heaven ...
With my family . I can accept that .
[ CRYING ]
REPORTER : Flight 180 ...
KIMBERLY : I know what I have to do to save us .
REPORTER : There are no known survivors .
KIMBERLY : I have to die .
[ MUFFLED VOICES ]
[ DEFIBRILLATOR CHARGING ]
DR. KALARJIAN : Ready and clear .
NURSE : Nothing .
- Come on . - Ready , clear .
- [ BEEPING ] - She 's back !
Epinephrine . Two milligrams , IV push .
I want her prepped and stabilized for ICU .
Welcome back .
They lost you for a minute there .
Hey . We did it .
Thanks to you , we cheated death .
[ LAUGHTER ]
- Would you like some wine ? - I think I 'll stick to our beer , thanks .
All right .
This is really great , Mrs. Gibbons .
Thank you so much for inviting us .
It 's our pleasure .
- How are you doing , Kimberly ? - Good . Yeah .
I had a fun summer .
I don 't know , I guess things are pretty much getting back to normal .
Brian , I think you better go check that barbecue .
Hey , careful . Those things are dangerous .
Trust me . I think I 've been through closer calls .
Yeah , me too .
Dad , you should tell them about the news van thing .
What 's that ?
Brian was almost hit by that news van that day in the field .
And your friend Rory , he pulled him back at the last second .
Saved his life .
MRS. GIBBONS : You never told me that , Peter .
Boy , that was lucky .
Brian !
[ SCREAMING ]
♪ I 'm right behind you
♪ here I come
♪ let me remind you
♪ you 're on the run
♪ my name is death
♪ come taste my peppermint-laced breath ♪
♪ all lights are diamonds
♪ behind dark glass
♪ she leans toward me
♪ a forward pass
♪ in the blood , come-a , come-a cow cud ♪
♪ nobody really cares about you now , bud ♪
♪ pay the price , roll the dice run the maze like-a mice ♪
♪ ashes ever turn to dust for the two of us ♪
♪ my name is death
♪ come taste my peppermint-laced breath ♪
♪ come taste , come taste
♪ come to the party
♪ the price is free
♪ you seem to persist hanging on the fount beauty ♪
♪ my name is death
♪ come taste my peppermint-laced breath ♪
♪ come taste my
♪ peppermint-laced
♪ my name is ...
♪ Death .
[ INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYS ]